<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!-- mcm menu (mandatory) -->

	<string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_welcome">
		<text>NPE Welcome</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_welcome_title">
		<text>New Player Experience</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_welcome_introduction">
		<text>Introduction</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_npe_welcome_set_title">
		<text>New Player Experience Introduction</text>
	</string>
	<!-- deck_welcome -->

	<string id="ui_npe_welcome_card_01_title">
		<text>%c[d_cyan]Welcome to the New Player Experience</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_npe_welcome_card_01_description">
		<text>You have installed the New Player Experience mod, NPE in brief. 
		\n
		\n
		NPE is a tutorial system that aims to help new players to get started in the game.
		\n
		\n
		Mods that add tutorials using NPE will be able to use this system to guide new players through their content. 
		\n
		\n
		A tutorial or deck, is a series of cards that are displayed to player when specific conditions are met (contexes).
		\n
		\n
		For example, starting the game, opening a stash, looting an item, or talking to an NPC, etc.
		\n
		\n
		You can find more information about NPE on the mod page on the ModDb website.
		</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="ui_npe_welcome_card_02_title">
		<text>%c[d_cyan]Access the NPE MCM menu</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_npe_welcome_card_02_description">
		<text>NPE has its own MCM menu where you can configure the NPE system to your liking.
		\n
		\n
		Open the MCM menu and navitate to New Player Experience and General Settings to configure the NPE system.
		\n
		\n
		The most important setting is Enable. If this is set to false (unchecked), the NPE system will not run.
		</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="ui_npe_welcome_card_03_title">
		<text>%c[d_cyan]Check all the NPE Modules avaliable to you</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_npe_welcome_card_04_description">
		<text>The NPE system is modular, meaning that you can add or remove modules that add tutorials to the game.
		\n
		\n
		Mods can add their own tutorials (deck) using NPE, as a series of cards (sets) that are displayed to the player when specific conditions are met.
		\n
		\n
		In the New Player Experience MCM menu tab, there will be listed other tabs each representing a module that adds tutorials to the game. 
		\n
		\n
		The module page will show you the sets that are added by the module. Each set setting shows if the set has been played or not, already. They all start disabled.
		\n
		\n	
		If a set has been played to you, e.g. you have seen the tutorial, the setting will be enabled (checked)
		\n
		\n
		You can uncheck already played sets to see them again. 
		</text>
	</string>	
</string_table>
